Guide to the E. Wight Bakke papers, 1929-1971 [bulk 1945-1970].
Bakke, E. Wight papers, 1929-1971 [bulk 1945-1970].
- Series V. Subject files.
  - Manpower. Includes papers by Daniel Quinn Mills, Sar Levitan, Jeffrey Burt, and Eli Ginzberg. (Box 4, Folder 24-26)
  - Manpower. OECD papers, 1966-1968. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Norway project. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Norwegian language materials. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Student movements, international. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Trade Union Government Concepts and Perspectives. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Series VI. Professional boards, task forces, and committees.
  Includes minutes and reports.
  - National Manpower Policy Task Force: Correspondence. (In alphabetical order by author's surname.) (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - National Manpower Policy Task Force. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - National Manpower Policy Task Force. Related papers. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Railway Labor Act. Report to the President, Recommendations, June 9, 1948. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Railway Labor Act. Report to the President, Interpretation of Recommendations, August 24, 1948. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - President's Fact-Finding Board Report. Bituminous Coal Industry, June 19, 1948. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - New York. Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations. Final Report, March 31, 1966. (Box 4, Folder 38a)
  - New York. Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations. Interim Report, June 17, 1968. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - New York. Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations. Report, January 23, 1969. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - New York. Public Employee Labor Relations. Selected Materials. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - New York. Public Employment Relations Board. (PERB) 1968. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - New York. PERB Pamphlets. 1968. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - New York. PERB. Office of Collective Bargaining. New York City Collective Bargaining Law. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - New York. PERB. Office of Collective Bargaining. Arbitrators 1968. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - New York. PERB. Office of Collective Bargaining. Board. Record of Cases Received and Processed, 1/2/68 - 3/28/68. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - New York. PERB. Office of Collective Bargaining. Mediation Register, March 1968. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - New York. Public Employment Relations Board (PERB). Office of Collective Bargaining. Impasse Register, March 1968. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 1967. Mr. Pomeranz states his case. The Financial Times, (December 13): 15, 20. (Item located with PERB material in files.) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. Robert D. Helsby et al. State of New York Court of Appeals. Briefs and Opinion. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Dartmouth College. Amos Tuck School. Board of Overseers. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Jonathan Edwards College. Administration, Faculty and Student lists. [1933]. [Bakke served on the faculty.] (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Quinnipiac College. Executive Committee. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Quinnipiac College. College Senate. Correspondence. 1970. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Quinnipiac College. College Senate. 1968. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Quinnipiac College. Committee for Evaluating Faculty Organization and Procedures. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Quinnipiac College. Faculty Tenure. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Quinnipiac College. Faculty Manual, 1967-68. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Quinnipiac College. Tuition, 1970. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous.
  - Contact address file. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Morningside College. Undergraduate class notes. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate paper. Hill Section community Survey. New Haven, Connecticut. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Oscar C. Bakke. Presentation speech at the Centennial Program at the Fair Grounds in Onawa. September 8, 1946. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - List of material removed from the collection. (Box 5, Folder 14)
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.